<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Articles</string>
    <string name="title1">Articles for training</string>
    <string name="title2">Articles for training</string>
    <string name="desc1">Welcome to our application, where knowledge is literally in your hands!\nWe have a huge library of articles of various categories for your continuous learning</string>
    <string name="desc2">Our articles are available at any time convenient for you. Use the app to study on your commute, during a break, or before bed</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="art">Art</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="guide">Guide</string>
    <string name="select_item">Select item</string>
    <string name="added">Added</string>
    <string name="sport">Sport</string>
    <string name="literature">Literature</string>
    <string name="mathematics">Mathematics</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="atitle1">Paintings</string>
    <string name="atitle2">Sculptures</string>
    <string name="atitle3">Photography</string>
    <string name="atitle4">Mixed Media</string>
    <string name="adesc1">Paintings is a form of visual art in which artists create images on a surface using pigments, colors, and techniques.</string>
    <string name="adesc2">Sculptures involve the creation of three-dimensional forms and figures using various materials, such as clay, stone, or metal.</string>
    <string name="adesc3">Photography is the art of capturing moments and scenes using a camera, often resulting in stunning and expressive images.</string>
    <string name="adesc4">Mixed media art combines different art forms and materials, allowing for creative exploration and unique compositions.</string>
    <string name="mtitle1">Rock</string>
    <string name="mtitle2">Pop</string>
    <string name="mtitle3">Hip-Hop</string>
    <string name="mtitle4">Jazz</string>
    <string name="mdesc1">Rock music is a genre known for its powerful guitar-driven sound and energetic performances. From classic rock to alternative, this genre encompasses various substyles and influences.</string>
    <string name="mdesc2">Pop music is a genre famous for its catchiness and easy listening. Popular songs often become hits due to their infectious melodies and lyrics.</string>
    <string name="mdesc3">Hip-hop is a genre that combines rhythmic beats, rap, and lyrics that reflect urban life. It has become a significant part of youth culture and self-expression.</string>
    <string name="mdesc4">Jazz is a musical genre known for its improvisation and complex chords. From swing to bebop, jazz offers a variety of styles and moods.</string>
    <string name="stitle1">Football</string>
    <string name="stitle2">Basketball</string>
    <string name="stitle3">Tennis</string>
    <string name="stitle4">Swimming</string>
    <string name="sdesc1">Football is a true battle for a goal on the football field, and team play will give you unforgettable emotions.</string>
    <string name="sdesc2">Basketball is a fast and dynamic game where every attack and defense are important for achieving victory.</string>
    <string name="sdesc3">Tennis is a sport where strength and technique come together in every ball, and the winner stays on the court.</string>
    <string name="sdesc4">Swimming is a sport that not only strengthens physical fitness but also brings harmony with the water.</string>
    <string name="ltitle1">Fiction</string>
    <string name="ltitle2">Mystery</string>
    <string name="ltitle3">Romance</string>
    <string name="ltitle4">Science Fiction</string>
    <string name="ldesc1">Fiction literature takes you on imaginative journeys to other worlds and times.</string>
    <string name="ldesc2">Mystery literature keeps you on the edge of your seat with thrilling whodunits.</string>
    <string name="ldesc3">Romance literature explores the complexities of love and relationships.</string>
    <string name="ldesc4">Science fiction literature delves into the realms of advanced technology and alternate realities.</string>
    <string name="altitle1">Algebra</string>
    <string name="altitle2">Geometry</string>
    <string name="altitle3">Calculus</string>
    <string name="altitle4">Statistics</string>
    <string name="aldesc1">Algebra is a branch of mathematics in which symbols and the rules for manipulating those symbols are used to study number theory and geometry.</string>
    <string name="aldesc2">Geometry is the branch of mathematics dealing with the properties and relations of points, lines, surfaces, and solids.</string>
    <string name="aldesc3">Calculus is a branch of mathematics that focuses on rates of change and accumulation of quantities.</string>
    <string name="aldesc4">Statistics is the study of data, including how to collect, summarize, and interpret data for various purposes.</string>
    <string name="htitle1">Ancient Civilizations</string>
    <string name="htitle2">Medieval Europe</string>
    <string name="htitle3">The Renaissance</string>
    <string name="htitle4">Modern History</string>
    <string name="hdesc1">Explore the fascinating history of ancient civilizations, from Egypt and Mesopotamia to Greece and Rome.</string>
    <string name="hdesc2">Discover the medieval period in Europe, a time of knights, castles, and feudalism.</string>
    <string name="hdesc3">Learn about the Renaissance, a cultural and artistic movement that transformed Europe.</string>
    <string name="hdesc4">Examine the major events and developments of modern history, from the Age of Exploration to the present day.</string>
</resources>